{
    "subject": "resource/G\u00e9rard_Debreu",
    "predicate": "ontology/institution",
    "object": "resource/University_of_California,_Berkeley",
    "human_readable": "G\u00e9rard Debreu was affiliated with the University of California, Berkeley.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9719976782798767,
            "question": "With which university was G\u00e9rard Debreu affiliated?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6698243618011475,
            "question": "What is G\u00e9rard Debreu known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6378346681594849,
            "question": "Where did G\u00e9rard Debreu work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6085152626037598,
            "question": "Who were some of G\u00e9rard Debreu's contemporaries and collaborators?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5266562700271606,
            "question": "Did G\u00e9rard Debreu hold any notable academic positions?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4942574203014374,
            "question": "How is G\u00e9rard Debreu remembered in academia today?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4707246422767639,
            "question": "What was G\u00e9rard Debreu's area of research?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.42791712284088135,
            "question": "Was G\u00e9rard Debreu a recipient of any awards or honors?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.37624591588974,
            "question": "What contributions did G\u00e9rard Debreu make to his field?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.28300824761390686,
            "question": "In what field of study did G\u00e9rard Debreu excel?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=G\u00e9rard Debreu was affiliated with the University of California, Berkeley.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5873_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What contributions did G\u00e9rard Debreu make to his field?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5873_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Was G\u00e9rard Debreu a recipient of any awards or honors?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5873_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What was G\u00e9rard Debreu's area of research?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5873_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5873_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5873_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5873_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5873_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5873_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5873_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5873_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5873_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5873_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5873_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the response in the requested format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents provide multiple mentions of G\u00e9rard Debreu being affiliated with the University of California, Berkeley, including his role as a professor of economics and mathematics."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"G\u00e9rard Debreu was affiliated with the University of California, Berkeley.\" Specifically, multiple documents mention his long tenure as a professor there, including details about his starting and ending dates (1962-1983) at the university."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}